# NGUYỄN BÁ HƯNG

SR. FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

### Contact

HCM, Vietnam

+84 869 052 629

bahung1221.github.io

bahung1221@gmail.com

github.com/bahung1221

linkedin.com/in/bahung1221

### Skills

FE - HTML, CSS, JS, VueJS, Tailwind

00000

BE - NodeJS

BE - PHP 

BE - Golang 

Databases - MySQL, MongoDB

DevOps - Unix/Linux, Server Management

DevOps - Git, SSH, Docker, GoCD

....

Mobile - Flutter

• • • • •

Soft skill - Task management, Collaboration, **Problem Solving** 

UX - UX Design, User-oriented thinking

### Languages

English (reading, writing, listening)

English (speaking)

## About Me

5 years of experience in the software industry, with nearly 4 years in the Fullstack Developer role (Frontend Heavy).

Currently working on an outsourcing startup, so I have the chance to work on all aspects of production-grade products.

I am also a member of Grokking VN, which is an organization passionate developers can share fundamental knowledge with each other.

My pros are research and self-learning skills since new things always pique my curiosity.

My target is to become a Solution Architect in the near future.

### Education



09/2015 - 09/2018

**Information Technology** 

### Work Experience

### SaigonTek 12/2019 - Present

#### Fullstack Developer / Solution Architect

- Developed 4+ products for VN & JP customers, mostly for the JP market.
- Worked on all aspects of the development processes: Requirement analytics, Consultant, Architect design, Planning, Wireframe review, Task Management, Development, and Monitoring.
- Product fields: F&B management system, Headless CMS, E-commerce, Social networking.
- Contributed to some OSS projects on Github: shopify/draggable, conwnet/github1s, and so on.
- Tech Stack: VueJS (Nuxt), Tailwindcss, NodeJS, PHP, MySQL, Linux cloud servers, AWS (EC2, ALB, S3, VPC, Route53, SES, and so on), GoCD, Flutter.

### Gogojungle VN 12/2017 - 12/2019

#### **Junior Fullstack Developer**

- · Developed & maintained an e-commerce system for the Japanese market.
- Worked on all three Frontend, Backend & DevOps teams.
- Tech Stack: VueJS, PHP (Laravel), NodeJS, MySQL, Linux cloud servers.

### Certificates

### **UX Design Fundamental - Nordic**

06/2021 - 08/2021

• Learned the standard UX design process. It helps me empathize with designers and product owners. Thereby creating a better product for the end-users.